Guide to the American Studies Program, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
American Studies Program, Yale University, records
1939-1992
RU 272
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
42.3
The records consist of search committee files, course descriptions and curricula, student files, and visiting fellow and faculty files documenting the activities and operations of the Yale American Studies Program. Also included are senior essays and board games created by students in the American Studies Program.
Yale University. American Studies Program
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 14-B (YRG 14-B), Records of academic departments and programs of the Yale Faculty of Arts and Sciences.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is partially restricted. See inventory for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of search committee files, course descriptions and curricula, student files, and visiting fellow and faculty files documenting the activities and operations of the Yale American Studies Program. Also included are senior essays and board games created by students in the American Studies Program.
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Universities and colleges -- Departments; United States -- Study and teaching; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Curricula; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. American Studies Program
- Course materials for American Studies 390a, 1981; Accession 1983-A-017
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - Course materials for American Studies 390a, 1981 (Box 1)
- Course descriptions for black history courses, 1962-1965; Accession 1987-A-109
  - Course descriptions for black history courses, 1962-1965 (Box 1)
- Student, fellow, faculty, and staff records, 1951-1979; Accession 1988-A-024
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2054
  - Ph.D.s
  - M.A. and M. Phil. Degrees
  - Visiting Fellows
    - Forejgn Visitors, 1965-69 (Box 21, Folder 354)
    - Miscellaneous, 1967-78 (Box 21, Folder 355)
  - Secretarys
- Records, 1939-1989; Accession 1990-A-025
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2024
  - Executive Committee, 1947-1974 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 3)
  - Executive Committee Meetings and Recruitment Meetings (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Recommendations, 1958-1965 (Box 1, Folder 5 - 7)
  - History of Arts and Letters correspondence miscellaneous A - Z, 1939-1950 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Academic Appointments for positions: correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Academic appointments for current students, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Provost's Office: communications (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Provost's Office: appointments (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - President's Office, 1951-1977 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Dean of Yale College: correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Director of Undergraduate Studies McFeely to Cowan: notes, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Director of Undergraduate Studies James McIntosh, 1972-1975 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Director of Undergraduate Studies David E. Stannard, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Director of Undergraduate Studies R. Warch, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - American Studies Majors: notices re intensive major, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - American Studies Programs in other Universities: correspondence [see box for specific programs], 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - American Studies in other Universities, 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 37 - 40)
  - American Studies 86: correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Former American Studies undergraduates: correspondence, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1970-1979 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Director of Graduate Studies, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Graduate School: Miscellaneous, 1966-1975 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - American Photocopy Equipment Co. [APECO], 1966 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - GNOMN Copying Service #950548, 1974-75 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - University Directory, 1967-72 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Application Forms for American Studies Major: Class of '72, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - American Studies Fellowships and Scholarships [Yale]: annual announcement, 1956-67 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Fellowships: 1974-75 and Prior, 1971-75 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Teaching Associates, Teaching Assistants and Teaching Fellows, 1967-70 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Teaching Fellows, 1973-1983 (Box 2, Folder 54 - 59)
  - Yale Reports WTIC: Yale University News Bureau, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - "Yale Reports": WTIC - American Studies Programs, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Readers, 1949-59 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Readers in American Studies Courses, 1964-67 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Outside Examiners in Honors Program, 1958-63 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - A.S.A. American Quarterly Dissertations, Fellowship Announcements, 1960-74 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Graduate Students, 1965-66 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - American Studies Graduate Students - Address Lists, 1966-79 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Student Activities [Undergraduate], 1966-69 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - American Studies Undergraduate Council, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - American Studies Publications: 65 00 100 360, 1956-65 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Meal Transfers, 1970-72 (Box 3, Folder 71 - 72)
  - New England American Studies Association [NEASA], 1967-76 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Director of Graduate Studies to Graduate Students: Memos and Correspondence. (See individual files for other matters), 1968-73 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Director of Graduate Studies: Notices, 1963-70 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - American Studies Association: General, 1963-78 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Studying America and American Studies at Yale -- S.E. Ahlstrom, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - American Studies Article -- Ahlstrom, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Sydney Ahlstrom: Bibliographies, [1976] (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - American Council of Learned Societies, 1967-73 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Modern Language Association, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - American Studies Original Organization, 1937-50 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - American Studies Program: Document Related to the Establishment of, 1946-69 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - American Studies: Barron's Questionnaire, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - American Studies Advisory Committee, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - American Studies Club, 1962-1979 (Box 3, Folder 86 - 87)
  - Faculty Club, undated (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - American Studies Club: Student-Faculty Committee, 1969-73 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - American Studies Graduate Studies Committee: Ad Hoc Committee, 1970-71 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - American Studies Graduate Studies Committee, 1967-71 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Statements on Graduate American Studies Courses of Studies, 1968-78 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Course of Study Committee: New Courses, 1971-77 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Courses [Graduate], Course Critique, 1952-71 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - American Studies: General, 1969-70 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Registration, Enrollment Figures, 1963-78 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Major Enrollments, Yale College, 1955-67 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Jobs: Graduate Students, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 98 - 99)
  - Graduate Job Information: Student Summaries, 1973-74 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Financial Aid, 1976-77 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Junior Faculty Summer Support, 1974-76 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Yale Graduate School: Report of the Dean, 1982-83 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Budget, 1949-58 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Budget: Current and One Year Previous - June, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Budget: Approved for the Current Year, 1965-66 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Budget, 1962-65 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Budget, 1967-68 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - [Expense Account]: Chairman's Fund - N.H. Pearson, 1963-67 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Budgets, 1965-1972 (Box 4, Folder 110 - 114)
  - Final Budget and Budget Materials for, 1973-74 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Budget Notes for, 1974-75 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Budget, 1975-1980 (Box 4, Folder 117 - 121)
  - Assorted Rainbow-colored Papers, Financial Statements, 1980-84
  - Assorted Rainbow-colored Papers, Financial Statements, 1984-86 (Box 5)
  - American Studies 35: American Architecture, undated (Box 6, Folder 134)
  - American Studies 59: Exams, Reading Lists, 1948-60 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - American Studies 90: Syllabus, 1949-50 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Religion 226, 1951-52 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - American Studies 92-8: Individual Leadership in American Society [Mr. Hague], 1952-53 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Philosophy/Am. St. 57, 1953-56 (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - American Studies 92-6: Romanticism in America (1830-1860), 1957-59 (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - A.S. 82: Goetzmann, 1956-62 (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - A.S. 88, 1957-63 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - A.S. 31b American Thought and Civilization since the Civil War: Strout, 1958-59 (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - A.S. 81, 1958-61 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - A.S. 87, 1959-63 (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - A.S. 92-1, 1958-63 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - A.S. 92-3, 1958-63 (Box 6, Folder 147)
  - A.S. 31: Mr. Ahlstrom, 1959-64 (Box 6, Folder 148)
  - A.S. 80: Langdon, 1959-64 (Box 6, Folder 149)
  - A.S. 92-4, 1959-64 (Box 6, Folder 150)
  - History 38: Patterns of American Thought - Goetzmann, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 151)
  - History of Art 51: Mr. Prown, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 152)
  - A.S. 86 Senior Essay, 1960-61 (Box 6, Folder 153)
  - A.S. 59: Reading Lists and Exams, 1960-61 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - A.S. 91, 1960-61 (Box 6, Folder 155)
  - A.S. 92-2, 1960-63 (Box 6, Folder 156)
  - A.S. 92-5: Goetzmann, 1960-64 (Box 6, Folder 157)
  - A.S. 37: Baybrooke, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 158)
  - A.S. 85: Levy, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 159)
  - A.S. 59: Lewis, 1961-62 (Box 6, Folder 160)
  - A.S. 59, 1962-63 (Box 6, Folder 162)
  - A.S. 91, 1962-63 (Box 6, Folder 163)
  - A.S. 59: Mr. Lewis, 1963-64 (Box 6, Folder 164)
  - A.S. 91, 1963-64 (Box 6, Folder 165)
  - A.S. 91.1-91.4: Dalzell, 1963-64 (Box 6, Folder 166)
  - A.S. 40: Hunt, 1964-65 (Box 6, Folder 167)
  - English 56: Mr. Lewis, 1964-65 (Box 6, Folder 168)
  - A.S. 59: Mr. Martin, 1964-65 (Box 6, Folder 169)
  - Early Concentration: Mr Folsom, 1964-66 (Box 6, Folder 170)
  - A.S. 88: Mr. Kaul, 1964-66 (Box 6, Folder 171)
  - A.S. 91.3: Mr. Levy, 1964-65 (Box 6, Folder 172)
  - A.S. 91.6: Minter, 1964-65 (Box 6, Folder 173)
  - A.S. 91.1-91.5: Mr. Dalzell, 1964-66 (Box 6, Folder 174)
  - A.S. 92.3: Mr. Levy, 1964-65 (Box 6, Folder 175)
  - A.S. 92.6: Mr. Summerhayes, 1964-65 (Box 6, Folder 176)
  - A.S. 59: J. Martin, 1965-66 (Box 6, Folder 177)
  - A.S. 91.6: Ruland, 1965-66 (Box 6, Folder 178)
  - A.S. 92.1: Ruland, 1965-66 (Box 6, Folder 179)
  - A.S. 92.2: Mr. Martin, 1965-66 (Box 6, Folder 180)
  - A.S. 31, 1965-67 (Box 6, Folder 181)
  - A.S. 59a: Mr. Lewis - Fall, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 182)
  - A.S. 88: Mr. David Hall, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 183)
  - A.S. 91-3: Mr. Cowan, undated (Box 6, Folder 184)
  - A.S. 91-2: Mr. Lilley, 1964-66 (Box 6, Folder 185)
  - A.S. 91-5: Mr. Henderson, undated (Box 6, Folder 186)
  - A.S. 91-6: Mr. Matlack, undated (Box 6, Folder 187)
  - A.S. 91-7: McFeely, 1966-67 (Box 6, Folder 188)
  - A.S. 91-8: Mr. Dalzell, 1964-67 (Box 6, Folder 189)
  - A.S. 91-9: Mr. Winter, 1966-67 (Box 6, Folder 190)
  - A.S. 92-1: Mr. Lilley, 1966-67 (Box 6, Folder 191)
  - A.S. 92-2: Mr. Dalzell, 1966-68 (Box 6, Folder 192)
  - A.S. 92-3: Mr. Redkey, 1967-68 (Box 6, Folder 193)
  - A.S. 92-4: Mr. Cowan, 1964-67 (Box 6, Folder 194)
  - A.S. 92-6: Mr. Minter, 1966-67 (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - A.S. 92-7: Mr. McFeely, 1964-67 (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - A.S. 36a: Mr. Reich - Fall, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - A.S. 86: Senior Essay, 1965-67 (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Readers' reports on Senior Essays, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - A.S. 146, 1953-54 (Box 7, Folder 201)
  - History 180, A.S. 150 Bibliographies, 1959-60 (Box 7, Folder 202)
  - A.S. 151: Potter (History 184), 1960-61 (Box 7, Folder 203)
  - A.S. 160: Mr. Pearson, 1954-66 (Box 7, Folder 204)
  - A.S. 167: Mr. Prown, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 205)
  - A.S. 168: Mr. Bickel, 1965-67 (Box 7, Folder 206)
  - A.S. 169a: Mr. Reich, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 207)
  - A.S. 170: Mr. Kaul, 1964-66 (Box 7, Folder 208)
  - A.S. 175: Mr. Broude, 1965-66 (Box 7, Folder 209)
  - A.S. 176: Mr. Goetzmann, 1963-64 (Box 7, Folder 210)
  - English 157: Mr. Minter, 1966-67 (Box 7, Folder 211)
  - English 162: Mr. Lewis, 1961-67 (Box 7, Folder 212)
  - History 190: Mr. Ahlstrom, 1961-62 (Box 7, Folder 213)
  - History 191: Mr. Ahlstrom, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 214)
  - History 194: Mr. Chisolm, 1966-67 (Box 7, Folder 215)
  - History 195a,b: Mr. Hall, 1966-67 (Box 7, Folder 216)
  - History 217a: Mr. D. Hall, 1966-67 (Box 7, Folder 217)
  - A.S. 180ab: Mr. Chisolm, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 218)
  - English 155: Mr. Martin, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 219)
  - History 190ab: Mr. Ahlstrom, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 220)
  - A.S. 217ab: Mr. D. Hall, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 221)
  - A.S. 251b: Mr. Prown - Spring, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 222)
  - The United States in Comparative Cultural Perspective -- L.W. Chisolm, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 223)
  - Undergraduate, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 224)
  - A.S. 31ab: Mr. Ahlstrom, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 225)
  - A.S. 36a: Mr. Reich, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 226)
  - History 38a: Mr. Hall, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 227)
  - A.S. 40: Mr. Levey, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 228)
  - English 56: Mr. Kaul, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 229)
  - A.S. 59: Mr. Martin, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 230)
  - A.S. 86 (Senior Essay): Mr. Dalzell, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 231)
  - A.S. 88: Mr. Dalzell, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 232)
  - A.S. 91-1: Mr. Fendelman, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 233)
  - A.S. 91-2: Mr. Henderson, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 234)
  - A.S. 91-3/8: Mr. Howe, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 235)
  - A.S. 91-4/5: Mr. Moore, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 236)
  - A.S. 91-7: Mr. Dalzell, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 237)
  - A.S. 91-6: Mr. McIntosh, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 238)
  - A.S. 92 Course Descriptions, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 239)
  - A.S. 92-2: Mr. Dalzell, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 240)
  - A.S. 92-3: Mr. Redkey, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 241)
  - A.S. 92-5: Mr. McFeely, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 242)
  - A.S. 92-6: Mr. Kaul, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 243)
  - A.S. 92-7: Mr. Parrish, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 244)
  - A.S. 92-8: Mr. Forrey, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 245)
  - A.S. 92-9: Mr. Chisolm, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 246)
  - A.S. 92-10: Mr. Martin, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 247)
  - A.S. 191a: Mr. Ward, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 248)
  - A.S. 192a,b: Mr. Ahlstrom, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 249)
  - A.S. 193: Messrs. Gowan and Lilley, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 250)
  - English 156b: Mr. Feidelson, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 251)
  - English 157: Mr. McIntosh, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 252)
  - English 161a: Mr. Holland (See 161b), 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 253)
  - English 161b: Mr. DeMott (See 161a), 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 254)
  - English 164: Mr. Feidelson, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 255)
  - History of Art 250b: Mr. Montgomery, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 256)
  - Religious Studies 202a,b: Mr. Ahlstrom, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 257)
  - A.S. 31a,b: Mr. Ahlstrom, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 258)
  - History 35: Mr. Barfield, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 259)
  - A.S. 36a: Mr. Reich, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 260)
  - Philosophy 37b: Mr. Kuklick, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 261)
  - History 38b: Mr. Howe, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 262)
  - A.S. 59a: Mr. Cowan (See 59b), 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 264)
  - English 56: Mr. Kaul, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 265)
  - A.S. 59b: Mr. Lockridge, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 266)
  - A.S. 60a: Mr. CLarke, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 267)
  - Application Sheet for Intensive Program, [1968-69] (Box 7, Folder 268)
  - A.S. 86 & 88: Intensive Major and Senior Essay -- William Lilley, Director. David Axeen, Assistant., [1968-69] (Box 7, Folder 269)
  - A.S. 91-2: Mr. Howe, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 270)
  - A.S. 91-3/6: Mr. Kuklick, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 271)
  - A.S. 91-4: Mr. Fendelman, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 272)
  - A.S. 91-1/5: Mr. Warch, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 273)
  - A.S. 92-1: Mr. Lilley, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 274)
  - A.S. 92-3: Mr. Thurber, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 275)
  - A.S. 92-4: Mr. Cowan, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 276)
  - A.S. 92-6a: Mr. Kaul (See 92-6b), 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 277)
  - A.S. 92-6b: Mr. Clarke (See 6a), 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 278)
  - A.S. 92-7: Mr. Warch, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 279)
  - A.S. 92-9: Messrs. Morison and Ellis, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 281)
  - A.S. 92-11: Mr. Pearson, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 282)
  - A.S. 92-12b: Mr. Ribuffo - Spring Term, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 283)
  - A.S. 192: Mr. Henderson, 1969-70 (Box 7, Folder 284)
  - A.S. 193b: Mr. Howe and Mr. Dalzell, 1969-70 (Box 7, Folder 285)
  - A.S. 194: Directed Reading, 1970-71 (Box 7, Folder 286)
  - English 161a: Mr. Trachtenberg, 1969-70 (Box 7, Folder 287)
  - English 157: Mr. McIntosh, 1969-70 (Box 7, Folder 288)
  - English 161b: Mr. DeMott, 1969-70 (Box 7, Folder 289)
  - English 175b, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 290)
  - History 108b: Mr. Kuklick, 1969-70 (Box 7, Folder 291)
  - History 191ab: Mr. Ahlstrom, 1969-70 (Box 7, Folder 292)
  - History of Art 251b: Mr. Prown, 1969-70 (Box 7, Folder 293)
  - Religious Studies 202ab (A.S. 31ab): Mr. Ahlstrom, 1969-70 (Box 7, Folder 294)
  - English 164: Mr. Fiedelson, 1969-70 (Box 7, Folder 295)
  - Director of Undergraduate Studies: D.D. Hall, 1969-70 (Box 7, Folder 296)
  - A.S. 25: Mr. Dalzell, Howe, 1969-70 (Box 7, Folder 297)
  - A.S. 36a: Mr. Reich, 1969-70 (Box 7, Folder 298)
  - A.S. 59a: Mr. Trachtenberg, 1969-70 (Box 7, Folder 299)
  - A.S. 31a-b: Mr. Ahlstrom, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 300)
  - A.S. 60a: Mr. Clarke, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 302)
  - A.S. 61b: Mr. Bontemps, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 303)
  - A.S. 62a: Mr. Clarke, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 304)
  - A.S. 65: Mr. Trachtenberg, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 305)
  - Religious Studies 202b: Mr. Ahlstrom, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 306)
  - A.S. 86 & 88: Mr. Prince and Mr. Warch, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 307)
  - A.S. 66b: Mr. Kimball - Spring, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 308)
  - A.S. 91: Core Books, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 309)
  - A.S. 91-1b: Mr. Stott, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 310)
  - A.S. 91-2: Mr. Kuklick, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 311)
  - A.S. 91-3: Mr. Worster, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 312)
  - A.S. 91-4: Mr. McFeely, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 313)
  - A.S. 91-5: Mr. Dalzell, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 314)
  - A.S. 91-6: Mr. Warch, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 315)
  - A.S. 91-7b: Mr. Moore, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 316)
  - A.S. 92-5b: Mr. Clarke, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 317)
  - A.S. 92-6: Mr. Chambers, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 318)
  - A.S. 92-8: Mr. Ribuffo, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 319)
  - A.S. 92-9: Mr. Warch, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 320)
  - English 56: Mr. Woodson, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 321)
  - History 31: Mr. McFeely, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 322)
  - History 38ab: Mr. Hall, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 323)
  - Philosophy 37ab: Mr. Kuklick, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 324)
  - Philosophy 46a: Mr. Kuklick, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 325)
  - Course Schedules, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 326)
  - A.S. 191a: Mr. Hall, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 327)
  - A.S. 192: Mr. Trachtenberg, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 328)
  - A.S. 194b, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 329)
  - A.S. 196a: Mr. Kuklick, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 330)
  - A.S. 197a: Mr. Leyda, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 331)
  - A.S. 198b: Miss Marshall (Afro-American 82b), 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 332)
  - A.S. 199a&b: Mr. Rice, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 333)
  - English 156a: Mr. Feidelson, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 334)
  - English 156b: Mr. Trachtenberg, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 335)
  - English 165a,b: Mr. Pearson, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 336)
  - Religion 210b: Mr. Ahlstrom, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 337)
  - A.S. 31b: Mr. Ahlstrom, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 338)
  - A.S. 36a: Mr. Reich, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 339)
  - Philosophy 46a: Mr. Kuklick, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 340)
  - Philosophy 37b: Mr. Kuklick, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 341)
  - A.S. 54a: Mr. Lerner (Political Science 54a), 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 342)
  - English 56a: Mr. McIntosh, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 343)
  - A.S. 57b: Mr. McIntosh (English 57b), 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 344)
  - English 59a: Mr. Trachtenberg, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 345)
  - English 59b: Mr. Henderson, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 346)
  - A.S. 61a: Mr. Bontemps (Afro-American 80-Ia), 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 347)
  - A.S. 86: Mr. Henderson (Senior Essay), 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 348)
  - A.S. 91-1: Mr. Byrd, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 349)
  - A.S. 91-2: Mr. Kuklick, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 350)
  - A.S. 91-4: Mr. Ribuffo, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 351)
  - A.S. 91-5: Mr. Worster, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 352)
  - A.S. 91-6: Mr. Kasson, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 353)
  - A.S. 92-1: Mr. Henderson, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 354)
  - A.S. 92-2: b) Mr. Pearson, a) Mr. Stott, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 355)
  - A.S. 92-3: Messrs. Kasson and Worster, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 356)
  - A.S. 92-6: Mr. Chambers, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 357)
  - A.S. 92-7: Mr. D. Price (Political Science 56), 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 358)
  - A.S. 92-8: Mr. Ribuffo, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 359)
  - A.S. 92-9: Mr. Warch, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 360)
  - 92-10: Mr. Erikson (Sociology 83), 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 361)
  - A.S. 93a,b: Individual Reading and Research, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 362)
  - History 22a: Mr. Warch, 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 363)
  - A.S. 25: D.W. Howe, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 364)
  - A.S. 31a: S.E. Ahlstrom, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 365)
  - A.S. 62a: P. Marshall, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 366)
  - A.S. 83a: C.D. Rice (History 83a), 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 367)
  - A.S. 86: L. Ribuffo, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 368)
  - 86 Applications, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 369)
  - A.S. 91-4: S. Stage, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 372)
  - A.S.92-3b: R. Warch, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 377)
  - A.S. 93a&b: Readings, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 382)
  - History 22a: Mr. Warch, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 383)
  - Sociology 11a: Warner, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 385)
  - A.S. 192b: Kuklick, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 386)
  - A.S. 191a: Davis, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 387)
  - A.S. 193a: Howe, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 388)
  - A.S. 193b: W. Clebsch, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 389)
  - A.S. 194: Readings, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 390)
  - A.S. 195: Research, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 391)
  - A.S. 196a&b: Trachtenberg & Warch, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 392)
  - A.S. 197a&b: Mr. Moore, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 394)
  - A.S. 18a&b: Marshall, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 395)
  - A.S. 199a: Rice, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 396)
  - A.S. 199b: Rice, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 397)
  - English 164a: Mr. Feidelson, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 399)
  - History 108a: Kuklick, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 400)
  - History 190b: Howe, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 401)
  - Religious Studies 202a: Ahlstrom, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 402)
  - A.S. 25: Mr. Howe, 1972-73 (Box 8, Folder 403)
  - A.S. 31a: Mr. Ahlstrom, 1972-73 (Box 8, Folder 404)
  - A.S. 31b: Mr. Ahlstrom, 1972-73 (Box 8, Folder 405)
  - A.S. 56a: Mr. McIntosh, 1972-73 (Box 8, Folder 407)
  - A.S. 59b: Mr. Trachtenberg, 1972-73 (Box 8, Folder 408)
  - A.S. 63b: Miss P. Marshall, 1972-73 (Box 8, Folder 409)
  - A.S. 83b: Mr. C.D. Rice, 1972-73 (Box 8, Folder 410)
  - A.S. 86: Mrs. M. Caskey, 1972-73 (Box 8, Folder 411)
  - A.S. 91-1, 1972-73 (Box 8, Folder 413)
  - A.S. 91-2, 1972-73 (Box 8, Folder 414)
  - A.S. 92-5: Mr. P.R. Metcalf, 1972-73 (Box 8, Folder 420)
  - A.S. 92-8a: Mr. G.W. Pierson, 1972-73 (Box 8, Folder 422)
  - A.S. 93: Directed Reading, 1972-73 (Box 8, Folder 424)
  - Changing Urban Conditions: The Rebuilding & Revitalization of Cities--David Storrs and David Barone (Trumbull and Calhoun Colleges), 1975 (Box 8, Folder 425)
  - Patterns of Aging in Contemporary Society: Spring Seminar. Brenda J. Stiers, Visiting Lecturer, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 426)
  - Political Cartoons Seminar: Spring. William Maudlin, Visiting Lecturer., 1974 (Box 8, Folder 427)